(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 5=
(15 Minutes Ago)
(Why are you in such a hurry?)
(Don't touch me. I'm ticklish.)
(I'll do it myself.)
So, what are you planning to do next?
Zhang Haotian
isn't someone who has the guts
to make a move.
So,
he relies on emotions
to manipulate people.
The less someone has of something,
the more they want to possess it.
I want to stir up that desire in him.
I think I can do it.
You have a plan?
I'm going to do something
even more exciting.
(Now)
(I'll make you)
(remember me forever.)
(Jiang Lai was afraid of heights.)
(Where did she get the courage to jump?)
How did you do that move?
(Happy New Year)
Sorry, Director.
I'll do another take after I rest.
Take a break! Another one later!
Thank you, Director.
What are you doing here?
It's all thanks to you.
You framed me
and made me lose my job.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from me.
(Zhang Haotian.)
(This slap marks Zhao Ke's
declaration of war.)
(The Jiang Lai you knew, controlled,)
(and hurt is already dead.)
(From now on,)
(I control this game.)
(She actually dared to hit me.)
(Interesting.)
Hey.
Haotian.
I still don't think this is wise.
Your priority right now
is keeping Lin Lulu under control.
I'll keep an eye on Jiang Lai.
I've clawed my way through all
these years for money and power.
I've never dared to gamble
with my own life.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I just suddenly realized
there's a strange beauty in madness.
Weird.
Cheers.
You guys have fun. I'm leaving.
Hey, you.
Let's talk.
Talking to me isn't cheap.
Do I look like I can't afford it?
No.
But you're not my type.
Then what is your type?
I like...
Then am I...
your type?
You are my type.
You are a woman.
Why are you butting in?
So?
Come to my place and talk?
Sure.
You're in the way.
Do you go with just anyone?
That's a nasty thing to say.
None of your business.
You said talking to you
comes at a price, right?
What? Got money to burn?
Enter any amount you want.
(Transfer Amount)
Fine, I will.
(Transfer Amount: -¥100,000.00)
Sorry, my queen.
But he offered too much.
So, sir, where do you want to talk?
(Endless Love; Combat Online Crimes)
We're talking in the car?
Mr. Zhang?
After you had Lin Lulu kick me out,
you started following me everywhere.
So tell me,
what do you want?
I already paid you.
What else do you think I want?
Now,
you're not afraid of Ms. Lin
finding out?
(I want to see just how far you'll go.)
Enough with the nonsense.
(Jiang Lai, stay focused.)
(You are Zhao Ke now.)
(You absolutely can't blow your cover.)
(Absolutely.)
(Don't let him get anything on you.)
Miss Zhao?
I think I forgot to mention something.
The money you gave me
is only enough for an appetizer.
(Haotian.)
(Zhao Ke really exists.)
(But if I back out now, everything
I've done will be for nothing.)
What about her appearance?
(Jiang Lai, how are you going
to make him believe you're Zhao Ke?)
(That's exactly how she looks.)
(She looks just like Jiang Lai.)
Miss Zhao.
Could you finish what
you start next time?
Leaving me hanging like this
is really frustrating.
(I'll find out who you really are.)
(Honey.)
(I want to have a baby with you.)
(A handsome baby.)
Honey?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
(Trapped)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot♪
♪To teach me how to live without you♪
♪I look up at the starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪